Hello friends, welcome back to our channel. So
today in this video we will talk about Nifty. Because
we haven't talked about Nifty for a long time, and we will see what kind of
movement Nifty can
see in the coming time. Apart from this,
we will talk about a stock which
I tell you in every video, an
idea where there is a very good
opportunity. In fact, yesterday we
talked about Adani Enterprises
and discussed it in great detail. If you have
n't seen that video, definitely go and
watch it. I like Adani Enterprises very much
and it can also give very good returns in the coming time.
Similarly, we talked about NCC, NBCC
and we talked about banks.
Right now PNB is retracing gradually.
S Bank is also coming down.
Keep S Bank on your radar for a little bit. If the
stop losses that I mentioned are
broken, then there
is absolutely no harm in exiting for once. Similar
interesting ideas for your future.  To keep
seeing you in the channel,
please subscribe to my channel. Don't forget to press the bell icon. Because
you are
definitely visiting the channel, but if you are not subscribing to the channel, then it is
my wish that just as
you helped me cross the first milestone
of 2000 subscribers,
I want you to
support me in the times to come as well. Today, let us
first talk about Nifty 50. The
movement I see in Nifty is a
little sideways right now. If you
see, we have
put a daily chart of Nifty. In the daily chart, the level which is
acting as support is
2195. So,
2195 is its support and
it is not breaking the support yet. If
you see, it has not broken this support for a long time.
From February 15 till now, this
support is still at 2195. And
if you say resistance above it, then
till where is the resistance? Its resistance is
22297.  So,
until 22300
is crossed, the next leg of the rally will not come around 22300.
And until it breaks the support of 2957, there is
no breakdown in it, so it is
sideways. There is no major
move as of now, nothing.
However, if you see
RSR SI coming around 60, till yesterday it
was 58, today it has crossed 60, then there may be some
bullish momentum
in the coming time. And
if you want to trade in this, then the best
strategy is to
book profit around 300 and if it
gets around 2957 or 22000, then
create a buy position there. So if you
are a daily trader, then this can be an
approach. And if you take slightly longer
swing trades, then definitely
stay with 2957. This is a stop loss.
Now,
I see a lot of value in the stock that I was talking to you about.
What is the name of that stock
friends, its name is ICICI Lord
General Insurance. I had
told you about SBI Life Insurance a few days ago,
now the stock of ICICI Lord General Insurance has come on my rate
and
what is the reason for its coming, if you see, it was
consolidating for a long time, if
you see for almost how many days it was consolidating
in a small range, then 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 13 14 15, it was consolidating in a range for almost two weeks
and this range was
almost from 1600 to around 1660, so
this range from 1600 to 1660 was
troubling us for a long time
and today it has come a good breakout, it has given a strong
close with a green candle and today it has gone
almost to 4 A 1/2, so from ICICI
This breakout in Lombard is quite good,
if you look at it now, then the
next stop that you will see was the
next stop at 1720 and 1720 has
already been crossed on the daily chart,
so the small target that was there has been
completed, so if you were
creating a position only for 2, 4, 5, then that has been
completed, if you have
not exited here then you can also exit and if you
also look at the RSI, then
RSI has also come almost around 80, so both the
indications that it is
going into an overbought situation and the
small box that it had made on the daily chart, if you look at it here also, then
its A level has already been reached here,
so the breakout of this box from 16 to 1600 to 1660, in this there
should have been a move till 1720  It has
crossed 1720, so
from the daily perspective, there has been a good move. It is
also going to go into an overbought situation. So, if you have
not booked profit, then you can book profit,
but if you keep a little anchor horizon in this, then in
my opinion, more money will be made
and good money will be made. In this, let me
move once on the weekly chart. I will
show you on the weekly chart
how it is on the weekly chart. If you are liking the video so far, if you
like the content or are
getting to learn something, then you
can at least give a like. One like is definitely a must.
I expect at least 203 likes on this video. So if you have
not liked it, then like it
quickly. And now let's talk about the weekly
chart. What you will see on the weekly chart, as
I told you, in this week, two weeks it was
completely sideways, there was absolutely no
movement. It has moved again today in this week, so
if you see,
it did the same thing earlier also, one big candle, this
one big candle, after that two weeks  A
complete side wedge, then a big candle and
then a two-week side wedge and then a big
candle, so this is a pattern that is
emerging in it, but you should keep this pattern in
mind and even now I think it will show
a lot of strength in the
times to come. Even on the weekly chart,
if you look at RAI,
you will see that it is 81.5 2, so from the point of view of RAI,
ICICI Lombard has already gone into an overbought situation. If someone wants to take a
position, they can wait a little.
After waiting a little, you
can think about taking a position in it.
Where is the support? The support is around 1640, which was the
move that came just this week, it resumed from 1640 itself, so
a resumed
move from 1640 can act as a support there only,
so 1640 1600, this is what
I told you, I had
drawn a box on a daily chart from 1600.
You can place support anywhere between 1640 and 1600,
however, a stop loss of 1600 would be a very
good stop loss. Let's
also look at the monthly chart
and see how it is placed on the monthly chart.
You will see a tremendous breakout on the monthly chart. This
breakout is a significant breakout
and if you have opened a position then do
not be so hasty in it because in this
you may
see a move of almost 21, 2100, 2150 because it has
created a very amazing rounding bottom pattern and the
breakout of the rounding bottom pattern has
also come around 1600. So this
level is around 1600, this breakout is here only,
which I have
placed a green color line in front of you, so if it breaks 1600 then you
can exit once and for all.
If your position is intact and you have
not done anything yet or you have recently opened a
position then definitely with a stop loss of 16.  Stay tuned, the
day it
breaks 1600, it will be released. If you
look at it from a long term perspective, then a
very good move can be seen
in it and the next targets are coming up to 2100 2150, so do
not be hasty in ICICI Lombard at all
and on the chart of RSID,
RSID of 69 will give you an opportunity, it is still possible that there may be a
slight retrace in the coming time
or it may retest the
level around 16, then it will be a very good
opportunity and there you may get
an opportunity for entry, this range is
so big, this range is from 1600 to
around 1660, if you
get 1660 on the day or whatever fall you get till 16 minutes,
Acumatica and then
whatever horizon you will keep, in that long term, the
target will be from 2100 to 2150 because
I do not have any personal holding, but as
I tell you in every video, I
In every video, if I do anything, I
definitely tell you. Like I
told you in the last video, it is possible that I may
exit Accel Tech. So today I have taken a
complete exit from Accel Tech and
I converted that position
to NCC, which I told you about NCC a few days ago.
I have taken my
position there. So whatever position I take
or wherever I square off a position, I
tell you all with complete transparency. It is
possible that I may also take a position in ASI Lombard in the future. I do
not have any position right now. That is why I am telling you that
whatever decision you take, please discuss it with your financial advisor. To keep
seeing similar ideas in the future,
you must subscribe to my channel. Do
not forget to press the bell icon. And if you
like the videos and like the content, then give
me a thumbs up and don't forget to
share it with your friends and family. As well, that is all for
today's video. We will see
you in the next video.  Thank you so
much